

Applicant for:

Senior Fullstack .NET (C#, JavaScript)

Orient Software Development Corp. 20 August 2021

Duy Tran

Main interests: Python, .NET

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

It would be great if you are looking for a junior software engineer.

I've worked for 1 year in the field of Automation.

Please feel free to contact me. Thank you so much.



Tran Minh Duy

Automation - IOT Engineer

Date of birth: August 7, 1998

Gender: Male

Phone: 0941781010

Email: minhduy.tran0708@gmail.com

Address: Ho Chi Minh city, Viet Nam

Website: https://www.facebook.com/profile.phpid=100007077526120

OBJECTIVE

- Short term: have a stable job, gain experience and skills.

- Long term: become an expert in the field of Technology and have the opportunity to become a manager or team leader.

EDUCATION

August 2016 - August 2020

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology

Major: Control And Automation

GPA: 7.81/10

WORK EXPERIENCE

September 2020 - Present

Công ty TNHH Hệ thống Tự Động New Ocean

Automation - IOT Engineer

Main responsibilities:

- Directly participate in the company's projects.
- Research and develop suitable solutions for customers.

July 2019 - September 2019

Công ty Cổ phần Công Nghệ TTB

Intern

- Participate in Daiwa Lance project
- Research and develop application for monitoring, control and data collection on the basis of cloud computing.

August 2016 - August 2020

Ho Chi Minh University Of Technology

Student

- Completing graduation thesis
- Project title: Process simulation, control and SCADA for pumping stations based on VPS centralization
- Regularly implement big projects and assignments in the remaining school years

ACTIVITIES

June 2017 - July 2017

Bach Khoa Green Summer Volunteer Campaign

Volunteer

-Together with other volunteers and local people in Ben Tre to build rural concrete roads and light up country roads.

CERTIFICATIONS

2017	TOEIC Certificate with score 705

SKILLS

Programming Language	C#, Python (basic)
Database	Microsoft SQL Server, MongoDB (basic)
Big Data	Hadoop (basic), Apache Spark (basic)
Mobile Development	Xamarin Form (basic), Flutter (basic)
Web Development	ASP.Net Core, HTML, css, js
Microsoft Office	Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Visio
PLC, Scada	Siemens, Rockwell, Delta
Other tools	Git, Docker (basic)